Inventory of the Paul N. McCloskey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 78)
  - Miscellany, 1976-1977 (Box 235)
    - Franchising termination practices reform
    - Product liability (Box 235)
    - BTU tax
    - CETA Davis-Bacon
    - Bottler's bill
    - Tax reform act
    - Revenue sharing
    - Weaver amendment
    - Food stamps
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 236)
    - "F--Foreign affairs" to "F--Foreign affairs--Southeast Asia,", 1976
  - Committee on Government Operations file. Conservation and Natural Resources Subcommittee, Central Valley Project, 1973-1975 (Box 237)
  - Miscellany (Box 238)
    - Agriculture information, 1978
    - Aviation, 1978
    - Airbags, 1977
    - Bike trails, 1977
    - San Felipe project, 1977-1978
  - Printed matter
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries publications
      - Tuna/Porpoise oversight hearings, 1978
      - Marine mammals amendments hearings, 1976
      - Fish and wildlife miscellaneous hearing, 1976
    - "The Evolution of National Wildlife Law,", 1977
  - Select Committee on Missing Persons in Southeast Asia file (94th Congress), 1975-1976 (Box 239)
  - Printed matter. Department of State "Background Notes" on various countries, 1970-1973 (Box 240)
  - Miscellany. Notes for McCloskey book--Chapter on forms of government in the world in 1974
  - Committee on Government Operations. Conservation and Natural Resources Subcommittee. San Felipe Division, Central Valley Project, 1972-1975 (Box 241)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 242)
    - "B--Energy--Oil Industry" to "B--Energy--Special energy group,", 1975
  - Miscellany
    - Renegotiation Act testimony, 1977 March 29
    - Commercial Law League of America
  - Printed matter. Revenue Sharing, by Willner and Nichols
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 243)
    - "F--Foreign affairs--Africa"
  - Miscellany, 1973-1975
    - Arms control and arms sales
    - Defense
    - Clemency-Amnesty
    - Cuba
    - Foreign aid
    - Immigration
    - Trade--Soviet grain and Cuba
    - Vietnam refugees
    - Wild horse, burro, tule elk
    - U.S. grain sales
    - Copyright
    - Law of the Sea conference
    - Stanford Medical Center
    - Marihuana legislation, H.R. 4520
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 244)
    - "A--District" to "B--Energy--Nuclear Power,", 1975
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1976 January - June (Box 245)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (246 246)
    - "X--Casework--Soviet trade unionists visas (Emmerson Street)" to "X--Casework--Ybarra,", 1976
  - Miscellany
    - Semi-conductor industry tax proposal, 1973
    - WEMA-Customs Bureau
    - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1977
    - Disposal site at Maxey Flats, Kentucky
    - Ray Handley--Solar energy
    - Jack Knudson--Ocean thermals
    - Varian Associates fusion research, 1976
  - Staff members' files--Rebecca Cook (Box 247)
    - Population files, 1978
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 248)
    - "E--Economy--Employment/Job training" to "F--Foreign affairs--Immigration,", 1976
    - "B--California--State water plan, 1973" (Box 249)
  - Miscellany
    - San Felipe, 1975
    - Coastal zone management, 1974
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 250)
    - "J--Environment--Corps of Engineers" to "L--Law enforcement--Religion,", 1976
    - "H--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare)--OSHA (Occupational Safety and Health Administration)" to "J--Environment--Bureau of Reclamation,", 1976 (Box 251)
  - Staff members' files--Ed G., 1972-1976 (Box 252)
    - Land use
    - National parks
    - Forest
    - Pipeline
    - Pollution--General, noise, water
    - Solid waste
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 253)
    - "H--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare)" to "H--HEW--Welfare,", 1976
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1975 (Box 254)
    - Maritime Administration and Coast Guard authorizations for fiscal year, 1976
    - National Advisory Committee on Oceans and Atmosphere authorization
    - Shrimp
    - Conservation and environment amendments to National Environmental Policy Act
    - Title XI
    - National wildlife refuge, H.R. 5512
    - Appropriations for wetlands, H.R. 5608
    - Fish and Wildlife Service
    - Merchant marine war risk insurance
    - Merchant marine political fundraising investigations
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 255)
    - "F--Foreign affairs--Latin America" to "G--Government--Federal Election Commission,", 1976
    - "O--Office--Interns reject" to "V--Press,", 1976-1977 (Box 256)
    - "P--Political" to "R--Requests--Referrals,", 1976 (Box 257)
    - "A--District" to "C--California--Golden Gate National Recreation Area,", 1976 (Box 258)
    - "D--Defense--Air Force" to "E--Economy--Communications,", 1976 (Box 259)
  - Staff members' files--Rebecca Cook (Box 260)
    - Population, fertility, birth control, migration, adolescents, 1978
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 261)
    - Maritime oversight and capital construction fund, 1975-1976
    - 200-mile bill, 1974-1976
    - Operating differential subsidy payments
    - Panama Canal transit, 1976
    - Maritime subsidy program, 1972
    - Public Health Service hospital systems, 1976
    - Soviet merchant marine, 1975
    - SS Savanna, 1975
    - SS United States
    - Title XI
    - Construction differential subsidy
    - Third flag, 1975-1976
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 262)
    - "X--Casework--Kahn's Corner Pharmacy" to "X--Casework--Simon, Charles,", 1976
  - Miscellany, 1975-1976 (Box 263)
    - International banking
    - ITC footwear
    - Parens patriae
    - CETA (Comprehensive Employment and Training Act)
    - Commodity agreements
    - Household head tax breaks
    - Hatch Act, H.R. 8617
    - Consumer communications reform act, H.R. 12323
    - IRS (Internal Revenue Service)--Treasury fringe benefit tax
    - Renegotiation act
    - Third budget resolution
    - United Airlines
    - Housing problems
    - Public works
    - Humphrey-Hawkins, H.R. 50
    - Tax reduction and simplification, H.R. 3477
    - Tax reform
    - Lytton Gardens
    - Common-situs picketing
  - Staff members' files--Ed G., 1973-1974 (Box 264)
    - Indians
    - No-fault insurance
    - Family planning
    - Water
    - Air pollution
    - Animals
    - Environment--General
    - Central Utah project
    - Energy
    - Environmental Protection Agency
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 265)
    - "X--Casework" to "X--Casework--Johnson and Maple case pending with HUD (Housing and Urban Development),", 1975-1976
    - "J--Environment--Noise pollution" to "L--Law enforcement,", 1975 (Box 266)
  - Printed matter, 1976-1978 (Box 267)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee reports
      - Panama Canal
      - Yacht hijacking and drug smuggling
      - Merchant marine miscellaneous
      - Coast Guard miscellaneous
      - Marine safety
    - Government Operations Committee reports
      - Government in the sunshine
      - Privacy
      - J. Edgar Hoover's FBI files
      - Customs Service mail opening
      - Airline deregulation and aviation safety
    - Other reports
      - Intelligence activities
      - Budget
      - Information resources and services
      - Federal advisory committee act
      - Court proceedings
      - Appropriations
      - Report of the Clerk of the House, 1977 January - June
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1976 July - December (Box 268)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 269)
    - "S--Invitations" to "S--Invitations--Korea,", 1976
  - Miscellany
    - Propeller Club speech, 1976 October 15
    - 60 Minutes--Maritime unions, 1976 September
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1975-1976 (Box 270)
    - General
    - Wildlife conservation
    - National Park Service
    - Ocean dumping
    - Whales
    - National wildlife refuge system
    - Aquaculture
    - Radioactive waste disposal
    - PCBs
    - Blackbirds
    - Steel shot requirements
    - Fish hatchery program
    - Endangered species
    - Fire management
    - Coast Guard appropriations
    - Delta Queen
    - FMC--rate increase
    - Oversight--national security
    - Maritime Administration
  - Miscellany (Box 271)
    - Special task force report on San Luis Unit, Central Valley Project (Public Law 95-46), 1978 January 1
    - Alaska lands, 1978
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1979 (Box 272)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission
    - Department of Education
    - Countercyclical fiscal assistance
    - General business
    - General correspondence
    - Department of Energy
    - Executive privileges
    - International energy trade agreement
    - Department of Natural Resources
    - Diesel and home heating oil hearing, 1979 June 28-29
    - Freedom of Information Act
    - Clean Air Act and coal use
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 273)
    - "32011--Inactive files--Weaver amendment" to "32097--Inactive files--United Airlines elections,", 1977-1978
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 274)
    - "25510--Labor--Collective bargaining for public employees--Pro" to "29570--Taxes--Elimination of Disc (Tax incentive)--Con,", 1978
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 275)
    - "14110--Civil rights--Gay rights" to "19560--Education--Vocational education,", 1978
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 276)
    - "24670--International relations--Mideast--General statement" to "25505--Labor--CETA (Comprehensive Employment and Training Act,", 1978
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 277)
    - "9110--Department file/Casework--Justice--FBI (Federal Bureau of Investigation)" to "9375--Department file/Casework--Trade, Special Representative,", 1978
  - Staff members' files, 1979 (Box 278)
    - Population, immigration, family planning
    - NARAL speech
    - Pete's amendments and past actions
    - Population crisis committee
    - U.S. population policy
    - Abortion and women's issues
    - World Health Organization--Agency for International Development--Inouye
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 279)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "20000--Energy" to "22020--Federal government--Civil service cost of living--Pro,", 1978
  - Miscellany (Box 280)
    - No-fault insurance
    - National parks and forest
    - Oil spills
    - HEW--Labor appropriations bill, 1977
    - Arts
    - Clean air background
    - International conference on safety of life at sea, 1974
    - Kaiser engineers final report on San Francisco Bay-Delta water quality control program, 1969
    - Study of California rural legal assistance, 1971
  - Staff members' files, 1976-1979 (Box 281)
    - Population
    - Agency for International Development--World Health Organization
    - Sri Lanka
    - National Institute of Child Health and Human Development
    - Depo-provera
    - Title X
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 282)
    - "25650--Labor--Right to work/Taft Hartley (14B)--Con" to "28006--Religion--Church/State--Con Mormon information,", 1980-1981
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 283)
    - "9065--Department file/Casework--Interior--Bureau of Land Management" to "9250--Department file/Casework--Small Business Administration/Parries, Garfield,", 1978-1980
  - Miscellany, 1975-1978 (Box 284)
    - CETA (Comprehensive Employment and Training Act), 1977-1978
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1977-1978
    - East Palo Alto--Nairobi College
    - School District
    - Cultural Center, 1978
    - Girl's Club of the Mid-Peninsula, 1977
    - Local public works
    - Yosemite MCA hearings, 1975 June 13-16
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 285)
    - Funding
    - International Longshoremen's Association--ILWU background
    - Amendments to H.R. 39
  - Miscellany
    - Final report of the American Indian Policy Review Commission, 1977
    - Office files, 1979 (Box 286)
    - Today show--POW (prisoners of war), 1972
    - Stonewall Jackson and American Civil War
    - Legal ethics book
    - Woodside power case
    - Statement on reapportionment, 1973 July 10
    - Independent Department of Justice, 1973-1974
    - McCloskey interview by Ted Becker for Becker's book, 1975
    - Ford speech on Justice Douglas, 1970
    - McCloskey statement on behalf of William Rehnquist, 1971
    - Gulf of Tonkin Resolution
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 287)
    - "7000--Personal--Book sent ( Truth and Untruth)" to "7154--Employment inquiry--Favorable,", 1978-1979
    - "7200--Intern--Miscellaneous information,", 1977-1978
    - "1025--General mailing list,", 1978 (Box 288)
    - "4500--Members of Congress,", 1978
    - "7250--Invitations/Scheduling--Invitations" to "7300--Equipment/Orders--Continental Leasing (CRT),", 1978
    - "20107--Energy--Gasohol" to "21106--Environment--Rare II,", 1980 (Box 289)
    - "18610--Economy and budget--Zero-based budgeting" (Box 290)
    - "19500--Education--Stanford" to "20026--Energy--Price Anderson Act/Information,", 1979-1980
  - Miscellany (Box 291)
    - Clippings about McCloskey, 1974 August - December and 1976 September - 1978 December
    - McCloskey press releases, 1972-1973 and 1975-1976 (Box 292)
    - Clippings about issues and McCloskey, early 1970s
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1973-1978 (Box 293)
    - Subcommittee on Oceanography
    - Subcommittee on Fisheries and Wildlife Conservation and the Environment
    - NOAA Reorganization
    - Ocean dumping
    - Oil spills
    - Refuge authorization and revenue sharing
    - Animal traps
    - GIFAs (Governing international fishery agreements)
    - Reimbursement of fishermen in foreign waters
    - Authorization of Tinicum, Seal Beach, Great Dismal, and San Francisco Bay Refuges
    - Tule elk, tuna/porpoise, wolves
    - Endangered Species Act
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 294)
    - "22030--Federal government--Civil service cost of living--Con" to "24650--International relations--Law of the sea conference--General statement,", 1978
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1979 (Box 295)
    - Minutes of Congressional board of visitors of the U.S. Merchant Marine Academy, 1979 May 11
    - "The UN Law of the Sea Conference and the U.S. Congress," by McCloskey and Losch, 1979 spring.
      Reprint
    - Lawfulness of Deep Seabed Mining
    - Alaskan lands
    - Klamath fishing
    - Papers, U.S. Court of Claims, Jessie Short vs. United States/Hoopa Valley Tribe of Indians
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 296)
    - "29599--Taxes--Restricted stock options" to "31150--Transportation--Railroads,", 1980
    - "17596--Defense--National Youth Service H.R. 6868 Panetta bill" to "17596--Defense--National youth service action demonstrations,", 1979-1980. (Box 297)
      Includes two files on selective service
  - Select Committee on Missing Persons in Southeast Asia file, 1973-1976 (Box 298)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 299)
    - "24740--International Relations--South Africa,", 1978-1980
    - "23500--Housing" to "24500--International Relations--Canadian-American relations,", 1979-1980 (Box 300)
    - "8885--Department file/Casework--Defense--Army--Ganshow, Alan" to "9020--Department file/Casework--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare)--Public Health Service,", 1979 (Box 301)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1977-1979 (Box 302)
    - Congressional board of visitors of U.S. Merchant Marine Academy, 1978 December 15
    - Sale of five obsolete vessels, H.R. 3094
    - Oil spill liability
    - Operating differential subsidy
    - Organizational meeting
    - Deep water ports
    - Ports and waterways safety
    - Maritime press
    - Sailing cargo ships
    - Rebating
    - Staff--Rules
    - Shipbuilding
    - Soviet shipping
    - Staff memoranda
    - Sweeney Ridge
    - Title IV
    - Trade relations
    - Transportation Institute
    - UNCTAD code
    - Underutilized species development act
    - Virgin Islands
    - Water policy reform
    - Cargo preference (corruption, "Dear Colleague" letters, campaign contribution, McCloskey amendments, Garmatz incident)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1975-1978 (Box 303)
    - Propeller Club
    - Seafarers International Union
    - Sea grant programs
    - Sea train
    - Senior citizen fishing license
    - Shipbuilding capacity
    - Shippers list
    - Third flag
    - Shipping magazines
    - Soviet shipping
    - Title XI--Caribe, Ed Turner
    - 200-mile limit
    - Tonnaging of container trades in 1980 (M. Y. Stone)
    - Transportation Institute
    - War risk insurance for foreign flag ships, waterway users tax
    - Wind-propelled ships
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 304)
    - "24660--International relations--Mideast" to "28030--Religion--Religious discrimination,", 1977
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1975-1978 (Box 305)
    - Illegal rebating
    - IMCO
    - Intercoastal shipping, H.R. 6503
    - Intermodal transportation
    - Jones Act extension to Virgin Islands
    - Longshoremen and workers compensation
    - Maersk Line
    - Maritime training and education
    - Maritime Administration speech
    - Mariner trade-in
    - SS Mariposa/SS Monterey
    - Antitrust exemption
    - McCloskey maritime speeches
    - Merchant marine oversight
    - Navy
    - Northwest Marine Works vs. U.S.
    - Nuclear-powered merchant ships
    - Ocean freight industry policy
    - Oceans policy
    - Oil tanker safety
    - Operating subsidy
    - Oil imports
    - Pacific Westbound conference
  - Printed matter. (Box 306)
    Hearings, reports, and committee prints from subcommittees of the Committee on Government Operations
    - Intergovernmental Relations and Human Resources Subcommittee, 2 volumes, 1977-1978
    - Environment, Energy, and Natural Resources Subcommittee, 4 volumes, 1977-1978
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1975-1978 (Box 307)
    - Freight forwarding
    - Gambling on U.S. passenger ships
    - GIFAs (Governing international fishery agreements)
    - Rebating practices and illegal rebating
  - Miscellany, 1974-1977 (Box 308)
    - McCloskey press releases, 1977
    - McCloskey views/statements on consumer protection, gun control, government in the sunshine
    - "Dear Colleague" letters
    - McCloskey floor statements/mentions
    - MIA (Missing in Action) Committee
    - Press--Correspondence by McCloskey
    - Questionnaires for endorsements
    - Legislation--Sponsored
    - Voting ratings, 1976
    - 17th Congressional District communications trust
  - Casework for 1979 (Box 309)
    - Syntex-Naprosyn case, 1976-1979
    - Central Valley power cases
    - Ames Research--Moffett Field
    - Zoecon/EPA (Environmental Protection Agency)/Altosid case
    - EPA/SRI case
    - Miscellaneous cases
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 310)
    - "X--Casework--Nairobi High School, East Palo Alto"
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "8890--Department file/Casework--Defense--Marines" to "9105--Department file/Casework--Justice--General,", 1977-1978
    - "28006--Religion--Church/state information" to "29598--Taxes--Private school discrimination,", 1978-1981 (Box 311)
    - "11030--Aging--Laboratory experiments on animals" to "14100--Civil rights--Freedom of expression (pornography)--Con,", 1978 (Box 312)
    - "21107--Environment--Lake Tahoe"
    - "21125--Environment--Klamath River"
    - "7350--Recommendations" to "8885--Department file/Casework--Defense--Army,", 1978 (Box 313)
    - "32098--Welfare--Food stamps for strikers" to "32121--Inactive files--United Nations--Vietnam admission,", 1977-1978 (Box 314)
    - "16100--Congress--Electoral College" to "17590--Defense--Budget reduction--Con,", 1980 (Box 315)
    - "8975--Department file/Casework--Federal Power Commission" to "9060--Department file/Casework--Interior--Bureau of Indian Affairs,", 1980 (Box 316)
    - "10000--Aging" to "16160--Congress--Limitation on congressional terms,", 1979 (Box 317)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1976-1977 (Box 318)
    - Merchant Marine Academy at Kings Point, New York
    - Maritime education and training
    - University of Delaware marine programs
    - Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (MEBA)
    - Women midshipmen
    - Congressional board of visitors
    - Panama Canal markup
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1979 (Box 319)
    - Oceanography Subcommittee
    - Anadromous fish
    - Panama Canal
    - Aquaculture
    - Fishery Conservation and Management Act
    - Tuna, whales
    - Shipbuilding
    - Endangered species
    - Deep seabed mining
    - Law of the Sea
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 320)
    - Panama Canal treaty, 1977-1979
    - Nongame Fish and Wildlife Conservation Act, 1978
    - Water policy, 1978
  - Government Operations Committee file
    - Auburn Dam, 1978
    - Humane Slaughter Act, 1977
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "21195--Environment--Peripheral Canal background,", 1977-1978
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1977-1978 (Box 321)
    - Maritime authorization
    - Maritime oversight
    - Staff memoranda
    - "Dear Colleague" letters
    - Maritime appropriations
    - Maritime administration markup
  - Staff members' files--Laurette Rash, 1971-1976 (Box 322)
    - Gun control
    - War Powers Act
    - Decontrol of oil prices
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 323)
    - Cargo preference, 1977
    - Law of the sea treaty, 1975-1978 (Box 324)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 325)
    - "24740--International Relations--Southern Africa--State, etc. 1978 position papers" to "25640--Labor--Right to work/Taft Hartley (14B)--Pro,", 1980
    - "20077--Energy--Carter energy plan--Sierra Club alternative" to "20107--Energy--Gasohol info,", 1979-1980 (Box 326)
    - "21123--Environment--Tuolumne Rivers" to "23550--Immigration,", 1980 (Box 327)
    - "17590--Defense--Annual report fiscal year 1981" to "17595--Defense--National Youth Service,", 1979-1980 (Box 328)
    - "31500--Veterans" to "31670--Welfare--School lunch program,", 1979-1980 (Box 329)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 330)
    - Cargo preference bill--Press and general correspondence, 1977
    - Cargo preference bill--Corruption (Box 331)
    - O'Neill correspondence
  - Printed matter
    - Congressional Record reprints
      - McCloskey on oil cargo preference bill, 1977 October 4
      - The strange case of Maritime Administrator Robert Blackwell, 1977 September 16
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file. Law of the sea, 1975-1978 (Box 332)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 333)
    - "21121--Environment--Stanislaus River letters" to "21205--Environment--Alaskan D-2 lands,", 1973-1980
    - "28500--Social Security" to "32070--Welfare--School lunch program,", 1977 (Box 334)
    - "14010--Civil rights--Abortion--Pro" to "16100--Congress--Electoral College--Reform,", 1980 (Box 335)
    - "17597--Defense--Registration--Pro" to "20075--Energy--California gas shortage,", 1979 (Box 336)
    - "21107--Environment--Lake Tahoe, 1979
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1975-1978 (Box 337)
    - Executive privilege
    - Justice Department inquiry into CIA (Central Intelligence Agency)
    - Privacy Act
    - Freedom of Information Act consumer's guide
    - Privacy Commission authorization
    - Presidential papers
    - Privacy Protection Study Commission
    - Mail opening activities
    - Polygraph
    - Redwood National Park
    - Reorganization
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 338)
    - Maritime Administration authorization
    - New maritime policy
    - New York shipping conference
    - National Maritime Council
    - Maritime speech material
    - Maritime policy--Response to Al May letter
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 339)